Awards

Gold Cube, Art Director's Club 2023 Awarded to the immersive site for *fossora*.

People's Voice, Webby Awards 2023 Awarded to the immersive site for *fossora*.

World's Best in-House Creative Agency, Art Director's Club 2023

Presented to Squarespace's brand team.

World's Best-Designed Print Newspaper, Society for News Design 2022

Awarded to The New York Times print team during my tenure refreshing its design system.

TDK Award, The Design Kids 2020 Recognized as one of 30 top emerging design talents worldwide.

Speaking

Tools for Collaboration, Common Fields Convening 2021

Co-led a workshop exploring strategies for grassroots co-creation in the arts, building on my prior research for the Guggenheim.

Circle Live: Design Trend Report 2023 Briefed a creative audience on emergent visual trends on the livestreamed show.

Writing

The Creative Independent 2022 ACOMPI on the Power of Building Something with Friends

The Creative Independent 2021 Worker-Owned Studio Partner & Partners on Building Tools for Better Worlds

Exhibitions

Embajada Gallery, NADA Miami 2022 An exhibition catalog designed for Cue Art Foundation was shown in the gallery's booth.

Poltergaze, **Buenos Aires** 2022 A typographic poster was commissioned for

exhibition by the experimental collective.

Select Projects

fossora, Björk 2022

Built a virtual environment for fossora, the critically acclaimed album by Björk. Built between New York and Reykjavík, The site unfolds into a lush, dark landscape.

Venn Diagramm 2022 - Ongoing

Founded a small interdisciplinary collective. Venn Diagramm explores publishing and the arts through open inquiry, creative interchange, and parallel play.

A Community is a Garden, The Guggenheim Museum 2020

Designed, co-wrote, researched, and produced an open-access toolkit for grassroots climate action; while participating in the museum's Research Practicum.

Print Design Refresh, The New York Times 2020 - 2022

Worked with the Directors of Print Design to codify the visual vocabulary of the print newspaper, introducing new visual storytelling tools and improving existing ones.

Experience

Independent Practice 2016 – present

Interdisciplinary work across design, art direction, and creative coding, specializing in culturally and civically engaged work. Clients include Princeton University, Phillip Johnson's Glass House, The Baffler, and the Undocumented Migration Project.

Visual Designer, Squarespace 2022 - present

Versatile contributor to the brand design team, owning or co-owning identities, campaigns, collateral, digital interfaces, photoshoots, and artist collaborations.

Designer and Art Director, The New York Times 2020 – 2022

Worked on design and art direction for the newspaper, collaborating across the newsroom to build layouts and commission illustrations for print and digital usage.

Designer, The Creative Independent 2020 - 2022

Web design and special projects for The Creative Independent, a repository of advice for creative people; as well as continued freelance collaboration since 2022.

Practicum Researcher, The Guggenheim Museum 2020

Participant in the Guggenheim Museum's inaugural research practicum, focusing on social good, sustainability, and creative practice for grassroots change.

Education

BFA in Communications Design, Washington University 2020

Minors in Writing and Art History with a cumulative GPA 3.75.

Software		Skills	
Adobe Illustrator	Newsgate	Art direction	Typography Visual Identity Web design Writing
Adobe InDesign	Figma	Graphic design	
Adobe Photoshop	Glyphs	Editorial layout	
Adobe Lightroom	VSCode	Front-end code	